so he goes into the kitchen to get a
glass of water the meantime his little
daughter looked to be four years old is
playing on the floor so I let myself in
and I get on my knees and I say to her
in Arabic
SMI what is your name so he comes back
in and he's standing there listening to
this what about the one where you
dressed up as a college kid yeah that
was so much fun oh my God that was was
the one that I enjoyed the
most like I say I was younger back then
my hair had no gray in it I was thin and
uh we got word that the intelligence
service station chief of an enemy
country was coming for his new
assignment and
uh how do you get to him right I mean
he's not going to be at the cocktail
party sipping a
martini so
uh I had a mentor at the CIA by the name
of gust
avatus gust is famous Charlie Wilson's
War I mean books have been written about
gust he was like a father figure to
me he was very controversial inside and
outside the agency killed a lot of
Russians a
lot medals
promotions couldn't get along with
anybody everybody hated gust and gust
hated everybody but he was a sweetheart
deep down you just had to know how
to deal with him like one time we were
working in the 17 November task force
together and I mentioned offhandedly
that 17 November's second victim the
chief of the helenic National Police his
name was malos that malos was a torturer
during the Hun and Gus grabbed me by by
the lapels and slammed me up against the
wall and he goes myos was my friend and
I said you better get your [__] hands
off of me old man or I'm going to make
you
sorry and he finally let me go and I go
what the [__] wrong with you I said
malos was a torturer I'm sorry if he was
your friend I'm sorry he got shot in the
head but he was a torturer and keep your
hands to yourself next time and
afterwards he's like I really respect
you for the way you
reacted
so anyway we were
friends so I called gust and I said gust
I got a little pickle here I said this
station Chief is coming and we don't
have a way to get to him and uh how do
you think I should play this because I I
want to cold pitch him even if it just
means frightening him so that he goes
underground so Gus said let me tell you
something I did back in the day in the '
50s so I wish I could take credit for
this but this was not my original idea
but it worked like a
charm so on Gus's
suggestion I got a book bag and filled
it with books so it was heavy and
bulky I found the guy's address which
was not hard and I found his car which
had a diplomatic license plate on it so
I went up to the car and with my book
bag I broke off the side view mirror
and then I picked up the mirror I went
to the next door neighbor's
house a Greek lady and I said is that
your your car over there I just broke
the mirror off no no she says it belongs
to the guy next door I don't know who he
is so I did that for cover
reasons so I go next door knock on the
door the guy answers and I start
speaking to him in
Greek and I knew he didn't speak Greek
and and so he says in English he says '
no no I don't speak Greek and I said oh
I'm sorry I said in English uh I said
you speak English I I'm sorry I I was
walking down the street and I I've got
my books here and and I I accidentally
hit your mirror and I broke it off and
the lady next door told me that it was
your car and I wanted to come and say I
was sorry excuse me sorry and and I want
to pay for it and he's like
ah damn it
now I have to take it into the shop I
said I'm so sorry it's it's totally my
fault I was just being
clumsy
and I'm standing there at the door he's
inside I'm outside but in in Arab
culture an Arab can never turn down a
request for Hospitality so I said to him
may I trouble you for a glass of water
and he's
like wait here he says so he goes into
the kitchen to get a glass of water in
the meantime his little daughter looked
to be four years old is playing on the
floor so I let myself in and I get on my
knees and I say to her in Arabic sure
SMI shm what is your name and she says
oh my name is whatever and I said uh how
old are you I'm four and I said what are
you playing in Arabic this is all in
Arabic so he comes back in and he's
standing there listening to this which
of course I did on
purpose and he says to
me what exactly do you
want so I stood up and I said listen I'm
not going to waste your time you're a
professional I'm a
professional this is my card with my
real name I'm from the CIA in Washington
your guy is going down he's going to die
you can die with him or you can be on on
the side of the good guys and you have
until 10:00 tomorrow morning to make
that
decision and I walked out and as I
walked out I said I'll be sitting next
to my phone that's my direct
line so I went back everybody's like
how'd it go I said I don't know we'll
see so we're all sitting there looking
at our watches the next
morning right at 10:00 the phone
rings and he says what do you
propose I said meet me in the lobby of
the Hilton hotel in 2 hours and come
alone and come
unarmed so we had six Security Guys we
were at CIA people were at every
table around there's a little cafe in
the lobby and I wanted it to be in as
public a place as possible so that if
you know all hell were to break loose
I might have a a little bit of safety
safety in numbers safety in the you know
public environment cops walking around
security
guards
so the guy
uh made a
demand I made a counter
offer
and finally I said to him look you're
you're not in a position of strength to
negotiate
here I'm I'm telling you what it is that
you're going to
do I'm not here to offer you
know
riches we can get to that conversation
at some point in the future but right
now you have to prove your Bona fites to
me and this is what you're going to
do at the end of the day he did
literally everything that we wanted him
to do we did make him
Rich he
survived he's a successful businessman
now thanks to your taxpayer
dollars and we were able to shut down
any threat that that Embassy would have
posed and it would have posed a real
threat to
Americans wow yeah that was a good one
that's a ballsy pitch man he was scared
shitless and like I say he was a
professional so he knew that every one
of these white guys that's sitting at
every table around him is armed to the
teeth and is working with me
yeah it's like you said before when when
the guy in the motorcycle when you put
the gun in his face and he said I'm not
afraid of your a gun it's the same
concept you walk into his [__] house
and start playing with his daughter yeah
he says like what kind of person just
going to walk in here and do that the
psychopath just came into my house and
now knows my child wild wow yeah that's
a good one
man what's up guys thank you so much for
taking the time to watch the interview
as you could probably tell this is a
brand new channel so if you got anything
out of this at all please like the video
leave me a comment tell me what you
thought tell me who you'd like to see on
the show um I see every like I read
every comment and I appreciate all of it
especially in the beginning because as
you know that kind of support goes a
long way on these platforms so most
importantly I have some awesome guests
coming up in the future for interviews
um so please subscribe to the channel so
you don't miss any of them but again
thank you for your time appreciate the
support and hope to see you again soon